Full-Stack Designer



Loves <u>UI/UX</u>, <u>CSS</u>, <u>UX writing</u>, and <u>using data</u>. Specializing in <u>Design Systems</u> & <u>Conversion Optimization through research</u>. 15 Year career grounded in telling stories and persuading through design. Thrives making complex visions clear.

Seeking: remote, permanent, positive impact, large projects, mentoring opportunities.

EXPERIENCE

iMARKET SOLUTIONS

Designer 9/2015 - PRESENT

- Designed custom, responsive websites for contractors with a 22% conversion rate average.
- Improved processes: helped establish a 3-day design turnaround, helped create & now maintain a pattern library, incorporated design critiques, and put in pace internal design principles.
- CRO Representative where we found insights through: AB testing, heatmaps, and research.

Developer 9/2014 - 9/2015

Developed 22 custom, responsive websites using MODx, HTML, CSS, and JS.

FREELANCER

Owner, etc.

- Ran a small design consulting studio in Gift-Economy.
- Lead projects for small companies like B&B's, carpenters, local non-profits, a music school.

ADLIFE MARKETING

Web Consultant

Built 15+ small sites for local businesses at startup. Did design, sales, account management, and development.

FIDELITY INVESTMENTS

Designer 2013

Designed and developed ads in HTML/CSS.

BRADY PEOPLE ID

Graphic Designer

2006 - 2013

- Designed brands and optimized logos to print on lanyards and badge holders.
- Managed 2 remote Designers. Went through LEAN training.

EDUCATION

SUNY ONEONTA

Graphic Design B.A.

UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN

EdX MicroMasters, UX Research and Design